I love this community and although my career is going to be away from here for some of their games, my heart has always been in my life who also over up here, we're going to touch with sweet hearts and she's in the crowd of the night, but her family is still being here, we do this is where we belong.
So coming back and doing everything I could, my ability to help I community and doing so much work.
This is a very important topic that I know, you can be emotional in terms, and that's okay.
It's important to most important things are running.
So what that means is that I want to take a look at how I've used with this tonight, we're really proud.
I've got Jean Langford, my drive here in the road road, and we should take a look at joining us in the trying to just the integral part of our community as we all know, and what great part of the city we are in in the town.
I also have a Commissioner Parnas here in the summer earlier.
Thank you for Mr. Parnas for being here, Mr. Parnas.
I also want to report to the Indian, it takes that partnership to make the community proud, and luckily we've just gotten a fantastic community of partnership.
So thank you all for being here and sharing this with us tonight.
I think we have a lot of pride in our presented.
There we are.
Thank you very much.
Thank you all for being here tonight.
It's amazing.
So here on stage, we tonight.
To my left here, I've got our council.
I obviously won't care around looking at the place to be in the micro booth, but.
So I've got our graduates and more to work.
And you're going to need for everybody.
I've got writing step, more to one.
I have a double board to.
Playing summer for board 3.
In our mayor, let's start.
On table, across the stage from here.
I've got.
I've been waiting for city attorney.
I've been.
I've got Joe Howard.
I've taken some long through.
Joe has represented the legal perspective and work with the tribes for many, many years.
We're really excited to have him up here with us today.
The shared information sharing a perspective in the tribes.
It's a completely entertaining question to do with my dad.
We also have from this time very important.
Very important is what could else track him.
Kevin.
The farmer.
He's leading council.
The council.
They stay civilification.
The majority of our council serves as a consultant.
But the current license.
It releases illegal matters.
Larry has been involved in these matters for many decades now.
And.
But those who use it don't so Larry.
Most importantly, he is probably one of the most passionate.
The fingers.
for that, for a great register.
We also have a today at a Walker Dino State of Boston State of Boston.
Walker is a associate attorney
of a day-to-day commandment of the D&WT.
As we know, the research is a primary area,
and I'm going to current in 1992 licensing,
to complain to DC appeal and the real licensing
of the service.
Also, if the D&WT have a chain of appeal,
Shannon is also a associate attorney,
and something really fascinating, wonderful about Shannon,
who is a candidate for the work.
The work is the federal energy and regulatory division,
and it's possible for oversight,
and it's a good name, and it's possible.
Shannon is a welcome information for the program.
I also had a nice office,
but I call this a coach for the Kept Tech,
and it is a hydrologist,
and probably one of the stores people had her in that.
But for all of the having it with us tonight,
we certainly thrilled to have one team.
But that being said, the title of the matter is in the tonight,
we're going to be going through,
and having some presentations, we're going to have a re-pistory
of the application on their work.
The Walker is going to show the presentation
of the United States,
and we're going to talk about what we're trying to do.
And then, Joe Howard is going to talk about what we're trying to do.
And then, DiTons is going to give us a presentation
of the technical studies of what we're going to do.
After that, we're going to talk about some pretty clear questions
that we're going to be sitting on the receipt
of the citizens and others,
and have some dialogue about that.
We're going to be a lot of concerns
that we're going to be out of here.
After that, we're going to actually open it up
to the forum.
We're going to talk about the rules of that engagement,
and how we can do that.
We're going to be using this mic right there for the stage,
and people have opportunity to remind us
to become asked questions of this man.
Because this really does need to be a back and forth time.
We want to know what's going on,
and we have the extra questions.
We have to send the information we want to know
if we want you to come ask us out.
If we, obviously, we can't,
we can answer the question.
We don't have an information we'll get it.
Because this is all about citizens' mind.
So, that being said,
I've asked everybody if signs are poems,
and if everybody says that,
but honestly, you can be really attractive
and we're going to have a presentation
for something else going on.
Everybody's going to have a talk of the work.
Also, the panel will be mindful
of your panels and devices before we begin.
We ask everyone to be caring about
the microphone.
We are recording your notes.
And we're going to put it in the video, and we're going to have one of the state's website, or we're going to view it later on.
So, I want to show you that everybody got a system in the video, and also here.
And I'm going to show you that we didn't hear it or they ought to worry.
If you're not speaking in the microphone, it may not be picked up on the video.
So, be mindful of that as we're presenting, and as you're asking questions.
So, with that, you might come up with a later report.
And we'll begin our presentation. Thank you all.
So, I'm going to be looking at the shots to some degree, because it's nice to be looking at the screen.
And if you have to point where you can't hear me, somebody else, and I'll try to adjust.
As the screen says, and it's probably going to be this time very important.
I'm going to try to be involved in studying and mitigating these issues for work.
Very well. I'm going to start on today.
I'm going to be touching on today.
One is the current light sense, which goes to make it 902 and it's probably scheduled to end in 2025.
The current version of the state civil litigation on the document was filed in 2008.
It's the third of the three major suits, the person was filed in 2004, the second one in 2001.
And this is the third one was filed in 2008 and it's ongoing.
And then it reminds us that the process is from 2017, currently scheduled to end in 2025.
And the license will potentially go for the 30 or 50 years.
My focus is going to be on the state civil litigation, but also what we've learned through the state civil litigation,
which will involve giving us some background and some history on the facts.
I'm going to go into this analysis, and it is an extremely fact sensitive issue.
Before I go further, I would really like to thank those of you that are coming back the second time from the Jim meeting with the somewhere to this.
And then equally thank those that are coming for the first time tonight, because we did do a similar version of this.
I believe in some of the slides and those that might not have seen it.
But I want to try to go and speak quickly through those.
It's my understanding, all of the power run presentations will be available for review through the city website.
And so, if you have particular questions, don't we go ahead and ask, now we're in the presentation and we're afterwards from May.
But then I expect that we were really good at this.
more later on if you're going to go through this presentation through the city of
site. So whenever you hear your word brief, I'm sorry, whenever you hear your word
brief, within a turning you want to take it with a great assault, but I will try to
be as close to that as I began. So what do I mean? It's really primary to this 30 years
of involvement. So I got involved in 1993, but I've gone back, I've researched
it all my back into the 30s. So I basically got an knowledge base that spans
the beginning concepts of the day on to the current. I also came in immediately after
the 1992 license was issued, and you're going to find out what I can see some
comparisons of why the city's still involved in that. I'm going to read my
licensing, and part of that was lessons learned by not being involved in the 1992 license.
I've spent over 10,000 hours studying and living in this area, which is an extensive
amount of time. Just down a few dates, I'm really going to try to stay away from dates and
all nations and stuff, because some of you are going to have a framework to put some
of this information. The van license was issued in 1939, it was closed in the 40, and this
is the point I really want to emphasize. Lead control was a part of this project from the
very, very first. They tried to present this and build this as a hybrid and I'm only, and
it was rejected. It was only improved when the flood control component was added to the data.
So, when you've currently seen a QRDA characterization of what this damn does, you will almost
probably see flood control as not mentioned. If you look at all of the early documents, flood
control was mentioned. This is a flood control project. This damn would not exist without the flood control
of the portion of the damn, and GRDA knew it was having to take on flood control portion of the
damn in order to be able to build the damn. One of those tensions that started very early on is the
core wanted the top of the power that will be 735. GRDA wanted the top of the power to be 745,
and the reason for that is GRDA said this night in 1939, that is very, again, if we don't have that
enemy of water elevation, we lose 20% of our single power. So, what's about on that? That is...
of itself was not a bad thing, but there was a recognition from day one that there was
frozen context where this power will exist, and in order to get the 735, GRDA made the
representation, all the decision makers, and in advance of what we can draw this late
down to 735. So let us go out to 745, but if we need to, we'll drop to 735. And I'm not going
to do this the whole way, but I want to let, you know, we have documents that work for everything,
literally everything I'm telling you, because of the time limitations that they have, I can
literally show you one of the documents, but here's an example, this is the 1938 letter from GRDA
written on our mission, which preceded it for, and it says that we've been using the normal operating
level from 745 as desired by the authority. The 735 has recommended by the Army, we all
will be to reduce the signal power by 20%. That's GRDA is the hangout to what that was for. And then
again, W Hall, it was an engineer at the 4GRDA, these are GRDAs people saying this, in 1938.
So it's in advance of threatening flux, school level can be lower, 745, 735, and 310, and 310,
and 310 days, and then down the low, and says, and can be lower than 730, if necessary. So
this day I was being built in the plan, that's what was being contemplated as to what could occur.
There was an early, and I'm really trying to worry with the latter detail, and I'll show you
this stuff that exists, that their information is here, you can go back and look at it, this was the early
year older, 735, and 310. So it's 45, 745, and it'll be a top of the top of the top of the
top of the top of the top of the top of the top of the top of the top of the top line. If these real
curves, it is a guideline, it's a target for what the way all nations should be during certain periods
of the time. GRDA now says, we have got to operate this way, this close to 745 as we can.
The current over is between 742 and 744, while when you look at how this damn was originally
out of the way, 742 or 740, 741, 742, that little bit, that little deep of the rule for
it, was the amount of those over 742. It would be very much deeper.
The majority of the year was operated below 742, so when you hear GRDA said that it has to be operated between 742 and 745, it was not operated at that point over the first 40 years.
It can't read these numbers, but these were the elevations, or it was the 835, 734, 734, 736, 736, 734, 734.
It's quite a regular, not exceptionally, not only in and out, regularly, this late gram of those levels.
About a third of the year, it was around 735, about half of the year, or 736, or above 340 or 740, and it was only made in June and July.
It was 742, or above. This is interesting, and I was complicated again, I don't expect you to understand it in the first place.
But this is why I just showed you the initial rule for them. You can't see these days down here, but it's 1984.
By 1982, they had already raised the light elevation from there to there on a regular basis.
That's roughly from about 734 to about 740, but just have that space in mind, and as we're here, they're also moving it up to a higher elevation.
Why is that a row of endless context?
It's rather than a context, this context, because it's been a hallway, which is GRDA's engineering.
GRDA's engineering for the same vacuum fridge, from there to there, which is still way lower than they're doing now.
That the sense that 1982, the result of the new, for a row per row, and the frequency of magnitude of flood events in Greece marked it.
This is GRDA's home engineering for the same range in the wake of emissions, and increased the magnitude of flood events marked it.
Then it's saying that the new operation has clearly reduced the projects that have severe coastal rainfall disturb in the high ground, but the launching year, and increased the frequency of this function in flood control.
So any time you hear GRDA talking about the late moment doesn't make any difference.
It sure made a big difference back in the 1980s and 2000s, according to their quality of the year.
This is that quote from a case, it's McCool, it's a primary client, and it's just been off in the northern case, it's in 2004.
And that, what's hard as simple as me, you know, so at all, we have this report about what we all
have in the US, apparently, in the States, to be important.
So this is another one of the work, is in California.
And what is it?
It concludes, indeed, there was only 3D increase through the years of normal elevation levels of the
light that resulted in the flooding of lands on our property.
So the increase through the years of normal elevation levels of the light, and you told
him to put it in the land of the stronghold.
So that's not, GRDA saying that, GRDA is engineers saying that the city is saying that this
is important, that the value of weight is all of the information that was out there and concluded
that the increase through the years of normal elevation has caused additional flooding and
that the city of right now, GRDA, got an amendment in 2007, the entire year, the operations
of about 7.42 in the amount.
And the new license that would be no longer, no line like that, it would just be GRDA to do anything
any time as long as it is 7.47.
So the point being raising it again, and we'll get into the impact of that in a second.
I'll give you just a few landmarks, this is just a rough schematic, but the top of the dam in
7.57, top of the flood control, the world of 7.55, top of the power pool of 7.45, 7.60 is the
amount of easements we're going to talk about, easements like the law, the easements
given the right of GRDA to put water on the ground.
The highest population of easements is 7.60.
Now, here's probably as good times as any farming you do, but I don't know, there are certainly
exceptions for many of things that I said, but what I say is 98.99% of political, they're going
to be a new one.
So for instance, GRDA has acquired a few easements here and there, and we'll maybe only through
the litigation that is about 7.60, but the vast vast vast majority of the easements, they give
them the right to put water on the ground at 7.60.
Project boundary of 7.50, we might talk a little bit about that.
The climate of the riverbed at the dam of 6.50, so that point right there is 6.50.
So we're going to be talking about the 3rd of the project operations, we're going to be talking
about the 20th between all nations, so at the 55 of the top of the power pool, I'm sorry, the top.
of what we will. And seven, third of five, which is practically speaking the bottom of the
tower of the wall. And then the entire dam, the entire dam is under forty and forty.
This is just a list of those that you think are actually going to refer to as we need to later on.
I'll try to highlight what elements should so are relevant for particular topic. But again, I'm
trying to have to throw you a lot of aids and a lot of numbers because they don't really think
that's conducive to understanding and trying to be conceptive to work. So as part of the
civil litigation, I wonder if we can find out about historical flood studies and the
values. Now this is one of the most important slides of the presentation. I can give you
ten different versions of this. But what is really key to this, this is the core. It's analyzing
between 1940 and 1948. It actually comes from a 1960s memo. We have a memo. I can show it to you
in the memo of the art and system of one of the earlier slides where I read about the 20% power
reduction. It's just hard to read about style and small. But what I'm saying here is that
in an analysis by the core in 1942, remember the dam started opening in 1994. So within two
years of questioning, what's going on. An analysis by the core to do indicated that the easements
in which the upper reaches up the light, which is Lyama, should have been a wire in elevation
of 760, and still elevation of 760. It looked at it again in 1948. The core submitted a preliminary
planning on the water based on the 1940s analysis. An studies in 1947, which indicated the easements
on an additional 11,750 acres, corresponding to elevation 7609 should have been applied. This memo
is 1960, but the information was available in the 40s. So since the core, the core and GRD had
a memo that then had the easements were purchased in this area. Again, generally speaking,
the vast majority of political, the top of the level of elevations in this area is 760, and they
had known for what's the map of approaching the 80 years that they had had it with easings. They had
no right to quit while they were at any property of 760. So people again, one of the talents
Why are people involved?
Why are we spending the money?
Well, here's one, four said in 1951.
There was a major flood, the biggest one
and record here is 1951.
And what the core is saying is, if it appears probable
that any steps towards acquisition of additional plans
would be considered an admission
that the operation of the reservoir in 1951
would cause damage to the area above those on which
Jesus had been alive.
So they didn't act because they thought it would be
viewed as an addition that they had fault,
that they weren't doing something they should have done.
In 1957, we had a southwest cyborg.
It says something along the lines with orders
are apparently accustomed to this condition, which
probably explains the actions of the collectives.
It's the opinion of this office,
but it would be much more not going to be much more economic.
It's the advantageous, bad to apply the additional flow of the Jesus.
So on the earlier slide, you don't want to talk about it
because it would be deemed as an admission
that we did something along.
Here, they're saying, well, people aren't writing about it.
They're not involved.
They're not in our core steps saying we should do something
about it.
So we don't need to require those additional statements
that we've been knowing about since before.
Here's another one in the sections.
Again, talking about 51 flow.
There's been a hearing out without a complaint
from those people in the event of the reality.
There was a recommendation that the acquisition
of the additional might have to be placed on an active set.
Throughout this 20-year period of time,
we ended up in the sixties.
It was always known in that before he's mentioned,
where we should have been in purchase of additional statements.
And there were economic, or other reasons
why the government shows not to do this.
But when you hear that this day
of has nothing to do with the flooding in my hand,
it is absolutely a category one out of the recent falls.
But what it reports about what is happening in this day?
As a general rule, GREA, the denial of the damage
caused by the damage increase elevation duration of the flooding,
multiple courts have been limited.
Results of an operation in principle,
the damage of the damage of the damage of the flooding from my hand.
That's where it's gone.
Well, what the actual reports?
1940-3GREA, the denial of the flooding and having this widening.
And what they're saying.
It was established that when heavy blood blood was blown into a stationary body, blood had a tendency to pile up, so that their elevation above sea level was greater, at the point where they flow into the stationary body, but at the dam, this effect is not as a bad one for them.
It was added at the end of the 20 times to different groups here in the February reference to Humph, that's the water elevation that's literally higher.
You heard the analogy here that I was shaking the water since it's all well, but it's time to do it.
And when the flood water is brushing down a river and a meat-sets stationary water, there's a Humph, and it's all back water.
And that's recognized as the endowment. It's not only the RDA and a 20-perfect, and this particular situation comes.
It's said to defend that's the RDA.
They're probably willing to build up to an elevation of 7.5.7.
And because of the result of that water, the level in wine of 7.5, if so many tells you there's no back water of that.
It's been known as the back water of that since 1943.
And then it says, as the result of the water scoring back down, called minus school grounds, causing damage in regard to which there is another speed.
There is no dispute. This is what it's happened. This was on a very high level.
And we're talking about a relatively smaller row of elevation.
And the area was closer to the dam.
But that in 1943, by almost Supreme Court, was a determination.
Exactly what we're still saying is happening. What has happened?
She already, you know, another row from that opinion.
Renew the dam before his wife and the dam is caused by a vacuum of blood water.
And not a fire, a vacuum of water is up such a level.
And it's not really quite a building where it's been decided to be required to, and did follow the instructions without all of the orders.
Pointing, being, here, a system.
Pointing is to, of course, answer is tough.
You build this dam, you operate it this dam.
Don't worry if there's a flood in London.
And whatever flooding is caused by the entire dam, is your liability and your responsibility.
So, whatever Court said, 1999 out of a district court.
So, here, we're almost at this camera.
Court's mind, here, here's a lot of the increased elevation and duration,
which was flooding about seven, six, and two.
That's needs to come out.
Nicole, 2014.
So one more of the fields that I've shot on earlier close with this opinion in earlier.
Federal government did not offer Nigeria a floodlight on its properties.
Statue decided to specify a GREA where we live in America's caused by a construction maintenance of the dam.
The existence of operation and its full dam was caused by the increase in the magnitude of the duration of the dam.
Another one from the cruel 60 years ago,
they go back and talk about why and not that said 1943 pays.
And basically says, GREA is why the third part is exactly as though it would form the ash on its own position,
which in legal effect, if it were it was not required to accept the provisions of the license and construct the dam.
So when GREA says or made it to it and to somewhat your level, your response to all the dam laws but,
and that core was correct and it didn't ever know that it doesn't have another goal.
Now with a period of difference in still in the old building, still in the old building, still in the old BLC 2013.
And it says, we find a common evidence for which the trap or the GREA is to court.
And as a prior fact, you're going to believe that it's taking the land of which property has occurred.
And this, right, so I asked it to be over one other time to be aware of this time.
And I don't know why I'm in front of the core of the BLC since I came over from the Indian, talking about what GREA said.
For a long time, I've been on July 10th, 2013.
GREA can see the taking of land on its properties for the purpose of that first time in the nation.
There's one thing, this entire thing we can all agree.
GREA is not viable for the natural flood.
That's not what we're talking about.
We're talking about the dam laws flooding.
And right here, in the core, GREA is saying, our dam laws flooding did cause taking a property in a highway condition.
I don't know if they may more than those conditions they had met.
This isn't the city context of GREA in India.
Another one.
Now we're going to continue my own analysis for this is in the litigation of regarding the current license, which I will need.
Now there's a talk on our mouth.
But check out these two crimes.
Don't just give them a lot of power and precision.
That's what you see to start.
You don't want to get this kind of language in an elephant decision.
The city reduced extensive evidence.
The previous damage was caused by flooding
attributable to the operation of this whole thing.
GRBA says that's not true.
The DC port of the hills with disagree.
The evidence of fence pull the dam's operation
has caused the flooding and the city of Miami is powerful.
Again, a DC serving pool, a house wants a DC serving pool.
It's recognized as the second highest order in the land,
immediately after the U.S. Supreme Court.
So I can't jump into the clouds at this point,
whether I want to make it crystal clear.
Everything I have just told,
every bit of information I have just told you,
how to serve GRBA, it comes from GRBA's engineers.
It comes from the four engineers.
It comes from another engineering firm called Lackon Beach,
which was responsible for those 40 studies,
one of those 40 studies.
How to serve Southwest power.
Later on, we have to talk about Dr. Forest Halley.
It was a rough rig.
His name went into that district court.
You've got the language front of the Auto Academy District Court,
from the Oklahoma Court of Civil Appeals,
from the Oklahoma Supreme Court,
from the United States DC Circuit Court of Appeals.
That's the information I just gave you.
You know what information I have in here?
A single piece of information offered by the city of Miami.
This is not Miami's word in GRBA's court.
It says that he said she said,
none of what I just gave you is a cultural basis.
What's front of the city of Miami.
Much about the city of Miami didn't even have any human.
It was other entities that were supposed to study.
It came to conclusions where the breakdown came and never did what they showed them.
And that's the real sad part of all of it.
So I'm going to switch gears a little bit and talk about the city.
And the city is involved in a lack of a lot.
Remember a lot of those fellows from the 40s, 50s, 60s,
year, the city had no inch which had no access to any of that information.
In the 1970s, the 70s, the 1970s, the 1960s,
the city flood had a moderate flood in the 1960s in particular.
And not let it do this one, but it should do this one here.
Jack Gell, come over.
I was not as something as you were.
And you started looking into it.
He went to the National Arts,
and he started finding some of these old documents
that were the sources of the information
that had already been released.
We got involved in the right told in 1993.
So then we went to the National Arts.
We went and did, and what we were called,
this is a record request to the Corps of Engineers.
We got their records, we got the records directly.
We went to the National Arts, we got them from GRDA.
That's where all this source of information
that just didn't give them to him.
Came from, we didn't get them.
And now, after the 80s, in the 80s,
there was still to be given an incorrect information.
They were still being told there was no map to it.
So at least they went to the ignorance, not being told.
Now we've been told there's no map.
Our weather work, we want to use it's not true.
And they knew it was true.
They were just trying to provide this community.
And it had work in the 50s.
Nobody was complaining about all this going on,
but those clubs of the 40s and 50s,
who wanted to go on and go on and be saw those mammals.
But I said, well, nobody's complaining.
So we're not going to do anything about it.
So keep all of this in mind, this foundation,
when you're asked, why is the city doing what it's doing today?
Why is it involved with this government?
So we're getting to the 1990s and 2000s,
and this is a real sad story.
The city is not in it.
They don't have the information that I've just given.
They don't know about those things.
I get involved in the 1930s, all that.
So what happens?
There's still being told there's no way in that.
You get US vision game and you get hope on wildlife.
So if you like that 1990, 90 UI sense.
It's like 15 pages of protection for birds, birds,
birds, magic, fish.
You know how much protection there is in the city when I am done?
Zero.
Because they weren't involved.
They didn't have a voice.
So again, when you ask why you're involved,
because that's what happened, you don't use it.
So there's a state still land, litigation,
and it starts being the acquisition of all this information.
And then on the revising same day, it's like the name of two folks
in the cycle, you can't extensate the way involved.
And here it is extensate.
This is a process.
It's a haunts.
It's a lot of money.
It makes a lot of time, but if you don't do it,
status quo, nothing's going to get better.
And you're going to continue to get flooded without any significant
relief.
So I did this section once before.
I'm going to do it again.
I kind of like to put some of the things I'm hearing.
to contact. So the fiction that I hearing is all of the flooding in Miami and the Spanish.
I just spent 15 minutes or hour long in Hawaii giving you 20 slides to show it's not all
that you are here to send when you can city of Miami and positive nature is not enough of the
emotions. This is my absolute favorite. I think of all the historical documents of just
you. All I want to tell you is historical evidence demonstrates that nature,
not project operations, the cost of the flooding. Rather flooding is caused by nature,
but natural things. And that's in a recent year, a publication here in the
city of Miami, 20, 20, 20, 20. What's the fact of the matter?
And it's just not quite said before, it's all about the earthquake.
It's called the NAMD, it's causing additional flooding in Miami.
GRBA is a lot of the forest. This is a nuanced slide that I want to go through quickly.
Remember how old and how about 7.45 and the flood pools,
tops out of 7.55 and GRBA sets, we are having any obligation or any responsibility
to flood control. We are having any liability for anything related to flood.
This is a combination of studies. Dr. Holly was a referee who actually was in all
the limitations and neutral fact of the doubt of this.
We cannot lose models and issues of this. Afterwards, GRBA is wanting to get a variance.
They are wanting to raise the length of this. So they are having the 2001, this is the
record, they are having the 2004. So maybe we can't guarantee GRBA is engaged, paying for
engineering to do a step and the study was. How much difference does it make?
If we have old nations, starting to make young nations, 7.42, 4.3, 4.4.
Try to cut to the chase. Well, he said it was, if you kept away 7.45,
you could just earn a million capital, 7.45, don't call the water.
Above that, there is still one point, 6.3 feet of damn caused flooding.
Just like yet, I don't think I can consider it. Even if you wanted to block offshore
response bill, block off the flood pool, this damn is still creating damn caused
flooding. Just from the power of all of them.
How do we know that? 7.62, that's above 7.60.
of 1.63 feet of flooding and heard the puppies since they had no right to create that
additional flood.
But that's a whole new one, but every flood hasn't told anyone that has its own day,
not every flood that comes with those same numbers.
But this is to guarantee that it's all engineers telling you that even just the power
it's causing flooding and the city of Miami above the easements that they have purchased.
So to make an industry to make it more, the whole day in a positive way, additional people.
There was 1.29 to 9 feet of adjusts, considering the power of the water,
the floods and the water that have gone straightened.
So when you hear 0.2 feet of additional flood,
listen to the listen to the words of project population.
GRDA tries to skew things and tries to create a favorable answer by asking the narrowest question
about how much difference you treat feet and the power of the woman.
And I'm going to touch on that little bit later.
But any time you hear a statement by GRDA that is available statement to them,
they call it's medical flooding and city in Miami, or no flooding in the city in Miami.
But through the phrase project about which, is it trying to take this entire damn,
and evaluating which is one little clever of the community.
This is just an example that I'm not sure if you're going to come across the hear from the project or something.
This shows what the damn flood's flooding was,
which is more in the nature of flooding of four or three weeks.
But it's not going to be a damn flood flooding that's occurring in Miami.
It's going to be like three or four or five.
How does that apply to you?
If you hear all of it, and if flood at three meter less, you wouldn't have been flooded.
But for the end of the flood flooding, but for what year do you think it's going to be?
Second question.
I am a killman.
So a little bit of a statement, this is a quote from a newspaper article,
so I'm saying, if we're just going to hold a whole bunch of churches, more land grease,
but if you're kind of going to make it go about that,
then I am going to ask kill any chances for future development and best of any time.
That's all one way to get it back.
What we're talking about here is to,
if I am the G.R.V.A, we're going to be interested in having any kind of apply out.
It's almost certainly the easements.
Not the same.
Not applying.
It probably all together.
And with only the property that I've already flooded multiple times,
that's already flooded in 86, 93, 94, 95, oh, 7, 2019.
Those are the kinds of properties that we've set to apply.
And think about the value of the impact on those crimes.
Those are the kinds of properties that I will argue later on,
and have never been built in the first place.
But we are not talking about that they're going to buy it down town property.
They're going to buy suburbs and have a flood of poverty.
They're not going to be buying or interested in property that only flooded in 87.
For those of you that may or may not know, seven was the second.
So when you're buying it, it's not like we're going to buy out of town.
We're going to buy out these properties that are in the flood.
And frankly, some of that's already happened.
You've had buy out some of that green space.
You've had properties that the homeowner has to lay down.
It's a good block away from it because it's the one I do in this.
It's one of the four times five times one end.
So we're not going to have a very limited opinion of property that would be subject to a important profile.
But by default, certainly it would be a piece of it.
Not a piece simple, not buying property.
And there's lodging to those property owners being paid something for the value of those properties
and then being able to move to a home.
But we're going to get into the project.
I wanted to go to work on the capital.
So going back to that 76769, the federal government had done quite a bit of supposed to do.
And what I was going to do back to the 40s, we would be interested in.
Any property in city and land are working out in poverty without that.
It's between elevation 76769, should not have been built.
It was built out of the 40s.
That never should have been long.
And if you go, we're going to step up the transparent, full salt,
let's go on and act it on it.
There wouldn't be no problem.
So it wouldn't be any excuse.
Yeah, I think should have been built beyond.
I don't know, that this is a great deal to slide.
I just remember, it should have been 7679,
it's that of 767, and this will be about 1,700,
and 158 years in all of the country.
So what do you already have years doing now?
What are you doing?
And not paying.
I'm trying to pay for it.
If the state's so the solution.
They pay.
It's a son who was flooding litigation in 1994
of Delta Coalition.
They paid son who took that opportunity
to have a whole new commission.
They're going to have a model to play in this language.
It's a city of Miami at all, versus the GRA.
And then this might be a good point to the mind, everybody.
The title of the lawsuit is City of Miami at all.
What that all means is, there are 449
and other things.
If the city of Miami, I'm going to vote in what drops
the city of the state's civil litigation,
that means we have 448 and instead of 440,
not reporting in the 49st of the 45th, we get to vote.
The city does not have a right, does not have means
to drop the state's civil litigation.
They only want to have 450 plaintiffs.
They only want to claim out of all those plaintiffs.
So that is going to go on.
And we are going to win, and why are we going to win?
And win because of those first-to-one slides that should.
GRA is a significantly flooding to the city of Miami
with the damn false flooding.
And I will vote for them.
What kind of use that the organ enters could be
by against beyond the strawberries
within the flood of all the times.
It could be employees, employees, and employees,
but it will be simple.
Almost never did they give me some help.
I understand that they have to be told they should be doing this
for years.
They hardly ever do.
They've started it a few times.
They've heard our guidelines to establish
they stop, they don't want to do it.
They try to enter and go and negotiate the products,
which is a well-being buyer, well-insider.
You can have great enterprise for the Eastman
or for a greater team or about what you do.
But we're not here about people that don't necessarily want to sell.
And during and at the very reluctant use it,
the domain can create a possible.
In my experience, they've gone one house
as part of the litigation.
They have lots of use, but it's not in home.
If you're creating a once-school, they want
to store a piece of the sort of flow
which is what they want these samples to store a piece of the
domestic name, and they don't just get to declare a lot of numbers.
That's not the way it works.
They have to pay a fair amount of income.
They must make every piece of collaborative
to acquire a property by a village dish.
If they can't come, they're going to re-apprent.
Then it goes.
So there are a lot of checks and balances, and as I said, when GERDA is pursued in this, when they get to the point of view of the commissioners for the appeal, and they get the number of what the government or how you is in that form.
So to make any decisions that GERDA is going to come in this by your city, that's not what it was.
The question is, are we officially, or are we're never going to buy one of the general for the findings from the property that's known?
They've made a statement that's made an actual approach or tried on the city.
So I'm probably going to only put it in a second.
We're talking about this repetitive property, and those properties are something that probably in a new control should be considered for some kind of eye out, or some kind of an easing purchase.
Because you're all brainier being taught.
You're not starting from ground disease.
You're already being taught.
You may be playing it again.
So let's make a sketch of pain for GERDA having a right to the point of view.
And I was supposed to now just work.
But that's a top way analysis.
We're talking about the little one.
It's my fault.
And I have an outside of the question all the time.
And I like all the lot of my people.
My thought is that you can get from me.
And I'm going to talk about tens of millions of $50 million of a million dollars to be paid for these people that have these properties.
And you can skew the city a little bit away from where all the damn cost of letting is incurring.
Get that out of the equation, raise the roads.
I personally think that's the very vital and the other costs.
So if it stands for all of them, we'll be meeting them.
That are having a few things to do with these things.
Or I'm trying to do it in the case.
So I just encourage you to keep an open mind.
What are we really talking about here?
This isn't GERDA coming in and not going to go or talking to you.
And it's a much different process.
And as far as we can get going, we'll do it.
If you do it with animals, we'll do it.
If you do it in the green and apples, we'll be dated.
There are other options.
We're going to talk about them in that series of slides.
And the one thing you should not have to, is let them do doing it.
You know what people say?
We should just back on, we should just let them stand as close.
Go for a little.
We'll stand as close as they're using your property and everything.
Why would that be a preferred option?
That it can be done understand that it can be a different part of you.
The third section is the raised in the length of not by any difference,
called current rule curve right now,
in 742 and literally 744.
For the regular reason, it was up to 744.
In the re-line sense saying,
they wanted to be 745 in the low,
so it's extremely likely that the length will be run in the higher level when it is written.
So we're going to have that higher characterization.
I'd like to have a little further explanation.
Before we were talking about the raised here today,
I'm going to show you that now,
but the raised from there to there,
that's what they did in the 80s.
Right now, the raised,
basically, wanted to raise,
since it's gone out over here,
so they're up here a little bit more.
But the wanted to raise it up to you,
based through the top of the bottom of the wall.
So when you look at this in the raised,
and then you're going to go to this increase,
they're very simple.
It's about the only increase that they did before.
And when they say the bottom before again,
that the new world,
the frequency and magnitude of the above,
it's increased rapidly,
new operations,
clearly reducing projects,
capacity,
the increase of the frequency on a function,
is quite control,
but it's clearly reduced.
So that was what they talked about the last time
that raised it about the same angle.
Now, we're saying,
when the raised at this next angle,
we're going to start to have anything.
I'm going to have a white with that.
It doesn't make any difference in the center.
But this thing about the project operation,
it's going to be about three,
except 40 to seven,
that's what G.R.A. wants to touch on it.
They talked about the bottom of the state,
the other was over 99% of the time,
and it's going to be talking about the back,
and that was six.
All we did was analyze that,
over time,
that way there's rigged a little bit
around between seven to three times,
seven to five.
The 20.
The entire day now,
this from six to ten,
seven to fifty five,
and forty five.
It's not really rocket science.
There's even a pair of three to three.
It's a 20 to three.
It's a hundred and forty five feet.
You're going to be able to say,
you know what, that's three feet?
You don't make a lot of difference.
Probably simply speaking,
it's not making a lot of difference.
But what you do,
this is making a difference.
of elevations that all ready to go out of the line to go to line.
And this is adding more water by the raising of light.
And system with the roaker of the threscent water,
and the new license, which is basically known for this.
They are raising the light.
That is going to have some in it.
Even though three feet is relatively less than 20 feet
is relatively less than 45.
When they say it's not going to be any different, that's wrong.
And they're skewing the question to be the most favorable to them
that they can possibly do.
If you're talking to a georgate person and they say,
this lake makes no difference because of the project operation
that's in how much difference it's in the day I'm positive.
How much difference it's in the day I'm positive.
You're going to get a different answer.
So, we already added the damage to everybody.
So, we have to know what it has to do.
For our guys who don't know what they're telling you,
if you have to do it at the care,
if you have to know what they're telling you.
But just because it's a little more flooding,
you have to put it in.
Nobody has to make any increase in the most flooding.
It's a pretty clear and almost nothing.
It's like we can actually count on it.
There was something called the storm again
and we had to manage the plan that was really involved in the recently.
We remember the very early plans and thought it was 75.
That's not a worldwide waste sign.
It's a good information about the management plan.
It was a plan to draw it out in the bank.
So, what they were somewhat cops up in the early,
thought it out.
It wasn't all that implemented and what the well-executed
was a very effective, at least it's something.
And that's not included in the Bureau of Education license.
It was about three of that protection.
There was no one there to do it.
Now, I wanted to have my conflict very briefly just
to the state civil litigation update.
I gave them a report to the clients and you're not all my clients.
So, I'm not able to say everything.
I would say it with clients.
In the setting, we had an extensive presentation
that was more to the one on the weekend than we went to the client's company.
Where we are, we have an agreement asked to the referee.
The referee in some states is called Special Master.
Now, I'm so lucky that it's technically sounding on the issues.
So, instead of the judge ruling on all these damn boss fighting issues,
we have a referee, some states call those special experts.
We try to add it to them, and they can promote the decision.
And while the man is modeling the natural and the damn boss fighting,
we've got versions of that going around the real licensing room.
We're going to make a decision, we're hoping that the faculty that's all
some time, let's get an order, we'll do this to have a decision.
We've just faced some results in the Refinity.
But we've done all of the other cases, and we've picked three, five cases,
trying them to reply those results, all they have to find,
and it's been very effective.
And it's definitely that part of it.
The people asked me, what kind of work,
what kind of work, how long will we be in 2008,
and it is just a streaming complex and extensive.
We're dealing with 450, we have a small one.
We've automated significant progress in our native state,
with some of the else, and we've made more progress in our six months,
and we've made them three years before.
We are getting to action, getting our three players to make significant progress.
And I've worked my most not to say good thing, it's not time to make progress.
But I have really, genuinely honest, at this time next year,
we're going to be in a significant point in where we are now,
and say this in a solution.
We're going to generate, we have three years of interest here,
one is the girl, I sense one is the state civil litigation,
and one is the licensing state civil litigation,
as the law has to relax, we are in courage,
we're going to win, it's the question of who,
so if anybody ever tells you that that case can't be won,
I don't know you've got all of them, I'm just going to say that's fine.
So, I take away the point,
we're considering getting going to party,
and trying to get everybody ready to go back to my push,
I'm going to go back to the point.
I'm going to go home, and I've been through with homework,
and homework, and homework, and over again,
by engineering partners, by the core of the courts,
if it is causing some better good flooding in the city of Miami,
then nonsense, the forties, here, here, here, there's a lot of the fora,
but one thing we've worked on with these years,
here today is not going to do a single thing,
but I'm going to go back to the courts.
That's my particular work,
And I'll be more down here tonight to the courts,
and I'll be here tonight to the courts.
So, thank you.
Here, you open.
I'll be.
So I'm walking to Knox E, I'm a famous guy from May, I'm based in Seattle, and I've been working for the city since 2018.
My firm is in working with the city's postcard team.
If she's related to the GRE, particularly its clerk license.
So, as spoke about this, at some point, I got the challenge called a Jew, and so, last quickly do some of that.
I'll give you some questions.
First, the things I want to take away from the Davis Retro main part of this discussion.
One, federal damages are meant to balance power output, and other aspects of the community environment around it.
Including federal. Next, is the point of the city in this process, is struggling to restore the place of upstream communities in that house.
As a virtual player, in May, in 1992, upstream communities did not really take a voice in mobilizing and proceeding and resulting.
The record in that, proceeding, and a license that GRE now operates under mobilizing different years.
It has not done well for the city and the communities that screened.
So, in the realizing process, so far, failure of the mechanism to realizing the same process started in 2017.
Currently, the current license still does not expire in 2025, it's a long process.
But we had good and recent success in this inferred to require GRE to gain more of a thorough stage, with a lot of the relevant scientific aspects.
In particular, what's called hydrology and hydrology model, where's the water realm?
And how does that change in different circumstances?
And also, sedimentation, so when that water is moving around, how does it carry silks and graphic and so on with it?
And how those different scenarios change, where that set them goes in the current.
So, we've got some back from GREA, under stainless glass ball, those studies are deeply flawed, we're currently working to try to correct them.
And soon in the city and hopefully others, yourselves included, if you're so implanted, we'll be finally in the comments on GREA, the license application.
I'll talk a little more about that. That's a little bit hidden.
Other takeaways here, what is successful?
Well, in the states of litigation, that's easy. You win, you get damages, GREA has to pay out.
It's more complicated in the licensing, because we're trying to balance all this in person, because they're not damaged.
But there are a lot of solution available to further.
that it can require as part of the license.
And there's even much broader universe of potential
components to a solution.
If you're dealing with actually negotiating
and start working together to think how to resume.
And finally, where we are in the process,
2023 is sort of the first best chance for the city
and others to make our own case in this license.
As opposed to just playing defense and trying
to make GERDA studies as good as we can.
So just briefly, because a purpose of working
tell last year the recording and the slides
from last June's come home in the city,
but I encourage you if you want a little more depth
into the water of the bridge so far and the licensing.
So the speed and data screen for me to work
and wipe a lot of it as hard as it is.
It was a really good discussion.
I asked you to have a picture to go find that in the city website.
But in the work of the conditions of the internal license,
since 2013, mostly in close with GERDA's attempts
to continue to be raised that room for a higher amount.
Also, quite a plain, with a sort of like a loss
that you might have a purpose that, of course,
alleging that GERDA can not acquire these,
and it's a command that it needs because it constantly flows out.
And therefore, slightly in this process,
it requires acquisition of only a fitting into the project.
First, Ms. Dan, which resulted in a DC circuit
of the ability to be hearing about,
which was just a disaster, I think,
one of the prize-of-home professional
for all of us working.
And I'm really wonderful, we're buying here.
You know, we work on these things.
And it's easy to lost in the weeds or the skirt edge
or hearing the nonsense from the other side.
It's starting to wonder if it's true.
It's like a half somebody else.
And what's more, somebody like a DC circuit,
or some people who look at him is in, that's nonsense.
It's really true.
And if you're going to read one court case,
that's a very short, reasonable one.
And then the licensing is the big thing, actually,
that I actually don't have any time to talk to you about,
I think, just about that.
So super quick summary.
Again, more detail, I'll ask you, because in addition,
but basically, I know how our names,
is that one's not very, very happy to get a license,
but it's the federal energy and rate of recognition
for the issues of those licenses.
And they last been 30 different computers.
To accept the license, the applicant, the licensee,
GREA, in this case, has to accept the conditions that
per puts along with.
And we perfect that includes operating importance
with the gorgeous expressions under,
but control situations.
It knows that has to do that.
and the liability comes with the one for less as it always says.
And by the way, those aspects of the licensing,
basically, we want to change the federal power.
It was adopted.
And thank you for that.
So the federal power access, the preferred conditional license,
the project, has to be best adapted to a comprehensive plan
for improving your development in the waterway.
And the comprehensive, basically, means what I said,
balancing all the industries, not just the power.
And specifically, the political, all in a bunch of others,
which are not all in the line to improve private.
But in fact, I know where, for example,
there's curvation issues with discipline.
But most of the rest of these are private services.
And all of these get balanced directly,
even the license issue by the current.
But of course, for it can only be balanced interest
that are represented in a decision record.
You have really perceived the work.
So that's what we're working on.
So let's take this in.
My album in the surrounding communities, residents,
are going to live with the outcome.
They're going to live with them.
There's license for 30 to 50 news.
And the effects of the operations during that time are going to last
beyond that.
You've heard someone that people were very excited
if you're really not going to talk about the size.
But in some ways, the first licensing,
maybe the best opportunity for really changing things going forward.
And the reason I say that is one of those balancing
policies that's required to happen.
And two, the realizes that is looking forward
across those 30 to 50 news.
It is not, you know, the state,
looking at the similar negation is wonderful in the sense that
the case law is about as clear as it gets,
the gerrogate has not lot of ability.
But the huge downsides in gagging,
what a poor community damages.
The goal in the realizes it is to set the parameters
for the next 30 to 50 years.
And it changes so that we reduce the blame.
And to the extent that they're making a damn possibility
that the gerrogate is part of the minute before it happens.
So that's the stakes of realizing
the second level of what's the harder.
Just quickly, where we are at the time,
well, I think, again, longer time,
I've been able to last you presentation.
Last September, gerrogate claims that it completed
all of the studies that was required by the firm to do.
December, we had our opportunity to comment on those.
And basically, we disagreed in a whole bunch of aspects
that their settings were sufficient
or correctly executed.
Also, gerrogate promises application.
So the next level of it is March 31.
Is the deadline for public comments,
including numbers by the city and any other stakeholders,
on the track-lices application.
That's too much later.
at the end of the management,
GREA will file its final license application.
So that is, it's a big aspect of FERD,
and that will be the application
that FERD ultimately decides on.
Sometimes, I have to add in there's so uncertainty,
but no sooner than August,
it will be the deadline for public comment
on the final license application.
So that's sort of the last best chance
that's wired into procedures
for what a new information on the record
of the state will use.
I say, quote, unquote likely later,
because it further decides to meet more
particularly environmental information
to do its analysis,
that it will push that and line down the road,
and there are cases in which
that has been pushed down the road by the years.
We hope it won't be that,
but it could easily be later than August.
Before our deadline of the final license.
And it didn't work, but the city is building,
you know, we've been having all this
push-and-pull about GREA studies,
and we're sort of on the downslope of that work,
and we're transitioning into the city sort of putting together
our own academic information and studies,
taking to some extent tools that GREA built
in the course of good studies,
because we succeeded in making FERD make them build.
These models are the highest in the time of the matter.
Taking some of those that are not good,
but are a lot better than nothing,
and making them work more, and using them appropriately.
So that's my right.
This is just a super rough schematic
of how you can think about all the different components
of FERD, and a different kind of way.
So my little diagram on the right
is sort of how I think of it mentally,
like almost a later, can you go flood?
You've got your water age on the right side.
And each of those colors is meant to represent
just conceptually a different component of FERD,
and in many cases, it's made each of those natural flooding,
and maybe you think of the blue block.
That's plenty of wood at home.
Have to hand it over to the color.
And there was lots of for which there would be no blue block.
There are places in town,
because it never would have been plenty of them up there.
And some maybe it doesn't flood those natural flooding.
That's another difference.
But on top of that, just by showing you,
putting the dam and the reservoir there,
as Larry said, that backs up a certain amount of water
upstream.
And so that's the next voice of the Larry.
Maybe it's added to it.
And that would be there, even, Jerry,
it just walked away from the controls,
and the dam sat there, you know, and come answer it all.
Then you get sedimentation over time.
And as I said, the dam changes the way that sediment moves
in the system, particularly, you know,
it's not rocket-sized, it's the best moving water.
groups, seven groups, gravel, sand, whatever,
more easily in this moment of view water.
So you put a huge body of soul in the water.
You used to be a frequent river.
And seven strikes, dropping out in the river is the reservoir.
Over time, that settlement, basically, it's just essentially
fills up space that water, but other ones have to fill up
and fill it up.
And so that adds to backwater of spring tants,
and the third book, I'm sorry.
So that adds to another bit later,
and I think that's just a growth of seven people.
Vegetation is a little complicated,
but there's good evidence that over time, a lot of land,
a long reservoir of river that used to be
to be open in the farmland has grown up with shrubs and forests.
And we think, you know, very hard we can do to
figure out what these are going to be.
It's harder to keep going in the farmland to let it open.
Well, you had that vegetation to places where water needs to flow.
What's happened?
It has a hard time to flow.
It gets slowed down.
It backs up more.
And you get another size of the river.
I say, if you change this, that's primarily for water,
sedimentation.
Potentially for vegetation growth.
And there could be some other effects too.
But those would be the big ones.
And so you could think of those as a other size of the pain,
or as widening those components that are over there.
And the operations really talk about M operations.
But as literature, how you operate again,
how high the reservoir is before the floodgates.
It doesn't matter if that water.
The higher the reservoir of the being operating in the water,
rather than the more that the inflow of water gets slowed down,
so that's the end of the water.
So I don't mean to suggest the relative size of these,
and those are very, very well-developed blood,
places of place in time and time.
Essentially, this is what we're looking at.
And this is what Giri is trying not to look at.
To say, the presence of the presence of the presence of the name,
Giri is completely ordered of the state.
And the cause, Larry, sites from there,
somewhere, while they say natural.
Well, the physical presence of the name
is anyone there on the national one of those states.
So the temptation of talking a little about that study in the next slide.
I think that basically sums up,
you know, as we transitioned into the city,
doing its own studies and directing here.
It's that we're trying to really get an angle of generating tools
of information.
Figure out the relative magnitude of these times at any given place in time,
with these sophisticated models that,
what I have for the given foot.
So, the temptation of one of those,
that I would focus in a little bit before me.
And this is a 2018, when I first started working on this project, actually, we pushed our
to require engineering in a to do computer model, the power of seven wood, wood, and the build-up
in this system and how it has that historically over many years.
They resisted that at a time, this sector, who worked, we said, yes, can, and well, ultimately
work a computer model in this system, we just laid that I mentioned this last year that,
no, I didn't, no, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, three years later, it came back and said,
yeah, we tried it and we were running a lot and we can't work, and we said,
no, yeah, it's still can't, you just do it right. And, ultimately, the environment and the technical
and so on, they have to, who looked at it, who looked at it, who looked at it, who was like, essentially saying,
yeah, it could be done. And so then they finally did it, there's a whole bunch of problems,
where we're going to mix it, and then we did what I wanted to basically brush some of the rough.
So we asked for, of course, to generate a fixed image of problems themselves, but we're also going to
work with correcting the model. In fact, one of our experts has identified an actual model on the market
for a few years, a seven-patient model of software, but the course of the college that is leading to
unrealistic outputs from, from Jerry's model, they didn't match. And we're developing work around it,
and it's important that when they, it's time to do different things, it's not going to be a problem, but we're
tossing it down to that person. So just to give you a sense, I mean, I think we're going to have a really serious
job here, I'm trying to get these things right. And I think, you know, frankly, that the group is
an important issue, basically, so they, they're trying to get the answer that they want, which is
one of the things I want to mention is contaminates them in transport. You're all probably aware
that the TARC groups from the TARC site and some of our other related, different websites and
tries to find a different background picture of TARC, and some other areas beyond there, contribute a lot
of Pettieville contamination, settings that come down, especially in the TARC group, and it's
worried that, but also a number of people who have screened the city, that's in the meowsha river,
a lot of them come down and screened their program down. The city asks for a TARC via GRA to do again,
another type of, let's just get them all out of town. I mean, look, we've established it. And the way it's
actually changes how the water groups around the way it goes and went. Well, the sentiment is in the water.
So, contaminates them. So, they're changing where the water goes, they're changing where the information goes.
And that, that aspect is actually never existed. And the entire art of the President's land is completed.
And so we asked for the required TARC via GRA to go figure out.
how does how they change the market?
In fact, where can you manage to go?
We asked for that in 2018, we asked for it again.
Here we go, we asked for it again the last time.
We're waiting on the first decision,
we had to make that their usual regular sort of time
on the way to the end of the January.
So we're still very hopeful about a lot of them
because they're the portal study and the minute-to-face
for it.
But that's great.
So with that, I'm going to head out to Shannon
of Neo, who has both said, used to work in the general health
of the health of the bird.
And it's going to be valuable to us on thinking
about how bird makes a decision, and how sitting,
and anybody else who's using the file, how that's
going to make the best use of the opportunity to set an intervention
in a way that can back the bird.
So thank you very much.
And I'll just take this in the larger to be working on this.
It's our challenging, frustrating times,
but this is a local community, and it's not going to work
for you, I'll work with this whole team.
Thank you.
No, I'm not there.
Yes.
No, I'm going to go through it.
Thank you.
I'm not there.
All right.
Could you be me off on that as Walker,
I'm going to have a chance to do a field.
I don't know what you can turn you out of.
Do you need to use the squash and you can see all that,
but I am going to need a program for you.
So I say, y'all look full of opportunity.
And I said, I'm going to be talking to people
to have to look at the department that have to be
full of questions, including around hydrodower,
but it's more important to know what I do now, what I use to do.
And as a developer, I use to set an clerk's box
with a general counsel, specifically on this,
that this task can't be realizing a hydropower project.
So, Walker, I'm going to just go over here,
but I think first issue of life is an incredibly holistic document.
They're trying to value a lot of different
and often community concerns.
And it's come up with an outcome that allows
to have a generation of power, while also respecting aesthetics,
reparation, the needs of communities and our projects.
And in order to accomplish that, a purpose of this generally
to do traditions and governance in our mental minds.
What's the effect?
those birds and bats, so they're familiar.
And she gave me a design and feathers,
dances, shrubs in such a way that we would see
a little of the offering that is intended.
And the industry of compliance has had a network
catch all of the powers, the damn offering
as part of the overall system.
And as an document, the communities were considered.
And first, in their role, the institutions
issue we were listening to and any subsequent licenses,
they're also a little bit tired of monitoring
and asking the clients to choose basically making sure
that the licensee can use to comply with the license
as their shoe.
And so part of our reference to this situation
is that we have a film, which operations
are not facing the inequality, and to repeat it,
we need the best fit for this community.
And we'll look at potential solutions
of, in our continued work on the current license.
And in what we use, new licensees that
are made by a report will look like going forward.
And again, that is the licensee, oh my God.
God will be an offering to be an expert within a few years.
So potential solutions that work to require
are a better, a better, a better, a better license
to change your day and again.
There is a 99%, 99%, 99% chance,
that we can otherwise have a little issue.
That's not really the argument here.
What we're talking about in these conditions
and that license and how faithful they are to the city.
So the things that require that license
are potential modifications to the way the data is operated,
potential infrastructure improvements, both even around them,
even in this monitoring of maintenance,
and improving the creation of other city owners
and the operations of the response personnel,
and in the case of various intermediates
from one event, flood demand for a great amount of activity.
And again, I was a witness to earlier,
the potential purchase of property rights,
to ensure that these lands that are already
in the right of the living, living, and flooded,
and in the open, as it will have some meetings,
and compensation to the end of the game, already
in terms of the private sector,
we'll continue to further have some changes.
And so, there you have, I am just going to tell us
to work together on the global long-term,
and I'm really interested in this perspective
about the new investment in the operating sector.
The process of the global power back very similar.
Again, I have an license, one of the rule on the list,
is that you have to have all end-of-end rates necessary
for the child, operate and maintain the higher project.
In your...
going out looking to make sure you have those in a race, here first on the gate, to negotiate the purchase with the link of theirs.
The federal power, our concrete grants have a different regulation for theirs, which can benefit you around a little bit of their shape,
they need to then work with the theme of digital sub-show prior to the necessary fields.
Again, they are not able to negotiate otherwise with the link of the grant.
And if you get to that point with the grant, you get to negotiate, it is required to create a fair mark without you for any land or a land where it is in touch.
So there's plenty of reasons for the Lariatians that they need to acquire what they cannot acquire otherwise to the negotiations with what they do.
And so, everything that we have talked about thus far, that's within the realm of your purchases.
If you go outside that and you've got potential for a offline consultant, you can even more creative.
This again, involves all of the worries coming in the years, able to close to the end here today.
You're looking for the record.
And what's possible, if you think outside of the structure of the product license, is full monopoly of potential.
We're looking at everything that can do, but also for, you know, if there's a piece of the damages from the simplification of the choice they have actually made.
There's funding for future improvements in the city, that's your infrastructure, that's your streets, your roads,
sewage, anything that you can have without a daily basis.
There's the impact on the development of the city.
There's the governance reform for the rate of the period.
It is operated on the board level.
There's potential, don't worry, legislative advocacy.
Make sure that legislation on the higher levels is, sort of, in such a way that doesn't prevent birth from giving a job,
and that the church care day operates with a project, responsibly, and as this one is actually, you know, a good number of your community.
And so now we're just a fun part of it, which is how you show your story with work.
There is a certain track you can throw it in a cellar.
In case you're not a little sweet, but we'll be excited a couple of slides.
And this again gets back to the plan I essentially thought what I used to do.
Because somewhere in Washington, you see, there is a birth attorney and a small office with a bunch of papers on their heads.
They are very busy. They got a lot of employment, but we know a lot of different projects, all across the country.
They need to get a decision about that's way to structural rights to those projects.
And they are doing the only way to decide decision on the basis of the information that is presented to them.
If other stakeholders don't get involved, then the information that is presented to them is pretty to see.
application of biodefinition C, which means
geradate gets a color, scorer, NLS, VD, provide
for my work with additional information that basically
all they have to work with is the geradate storage.
And those applications they are very intensive, they
have a rely ground, but they do not speak to what
I think is like to be a citizen of the fight, I'm not
going to have an operation that I've got to have
to do with my work, I've been here, and I'm essentially
presenting, and I think we can do a type of drug
order.
So this particular period of time, we're all going to
wait out of the pipeline, and actually we're all going to
20, 20, 20 in the further, is your opportunity to
share your story and soul to make sure that there is someone
who knows exactly what I'm going to do, and so attention
you have commanded in order to effect your agent changes.
I want to thank you for this one.
It's a salmon, that's great.
You want us to be out of my letter, and you want to get one of
the customers here.
You can see it's a hand in hand, that's it.
You can mail it right on to your permission, it will get
posted on the federal government website for anyone who
reviewed.
You also hope if you were someone who likes to do
their top line, they didn't even be here through you.
You can go to the first website, you can visit
the comments like, how did I?
It's quick, it's easy, you can do on the couch.
It's a great way to make sure that it's very low stakes
to be to get your story hold.
We love making even more low stakes and accessible for you to see
things.
Right here right now, if you want to be out of your boat, you can scan
this boat.
It will take you straight to the first comment on the website.
And to your comment, it's our project.
We keep one more time to work.
And so I'm going on, and this will also be through some of the
things by saying you can go back to our website and
in a time in the future.
The comment function is really set up to make it quick.
You can keep it in the premises hospital.
And you will need to enter some information as
because, again, this is more important than it is for you.
You're going to need to study the topic under the specific
technical project.
That's, as I said, P1 or P1 or P1.
And then you can decide to drop it.
It's quick.
It's easy.
I learned limited success characters.
So, you can comment on the website.
But you may not have your pre-empty like story,
short.
So, maybe you can comment on the website.
And also, you have progress prior or prior concerns
of your experiences, and I have something that should,
and you can all I could answer the first
consider as a takes of tannies in the opportunity to use.
Thank you very much.
And again, I mentioned that there is the inherent interest rate in your product, you know, a lot.
But if you don't want to offer any of the individual stories,
and you have a technical information that we're submitting,
they have a GREA story that they're telling their application,
but they don't have the experience of the system to rely on the product.
And out of the argument now, which, as I said,
you mentioned, wasn't there as a previous license,
because the product market got some place in the art.
After that, I'm going to need to bring out a virtual model,
how we can DM to the impact of your life.
For a full lot of understand, what it's like to have a really water in your living room.
You need to let the nodes of the baby actively,
and we'll be able to grab any provisions in this next slide.
So again, we'll be in place for the next part of the year.
So once you said live your comments, you push it button,
it's going to get those on the third website.
It will be in the record, in terms of you.
In need to know, notice, in the future,
like that, so if I may get something done,
we're going to be able to go back and back and back.
It's almost still our case.
So again, that's part of what we need to support it
and part of what we need to do,
and that's part of what we need to do.
I'm not part of what we should do.
After that, you can have an follow-up question
to view before the time you talk to you.
Again, you have an education policy.
She's all a David.
But you weren't sure I talked to you something, y'all.
I'm sure.
But I don't know.
So please don't hesitate to give me a chat of the report
to working with a few, and I don't know what we're going to say.
No, it's absolutely modern.
It's for us at the city.
And it's about to be very helpful.
We may remember everybody.
My name is Joe Coward.
And I'm the attorney.
And with the Jacobs Law,
I went for a new tribes across the country,
and had the honor to be standing in front of my boss,
and she landed, and I remember several of the tribes,
and I was probably over a month or many years.
I wanted to give you the perspective of the tribal movement
in the perfect places you were seeing,
and give you a little bit of background
where the tribes have been.
And where they'll be going to this process.
Fundamentally, I think the key thing to understand is
the tribes here, wholeheartedly, and the existence
concerned about being passed.
My own area.
is the Tribes Homeland, and my name is their home.
And the impacts that are occurring in this area
are happening in the future.
Fundamentally, the Tribes are wanted to work with
and have the honor of working with the city
and their team of experts have been valuable
in helping us engage in this process.
The Tribes want simply to work to ensure
helping the state of place to raise kids
to operate businesses and to have a medical school.
So it's important to think through the years of what we call
a blind spot in this area, in the election,
licensing in the dam in the 40s, 50s, 60,
really up until the 80s.
And it's especially true with tribes,
because, at the all-emotivist area, the Tribes
in this area, the 40s, 50s, 60s, 70s,
the time to channel the Tribes.
And having resources to engage in the dams' places
in the process just wasn't great physically.
We'll speak more to the impact on the Tribes
of the public, but also important was that it's
generally when you forward with their licensing,
neither G-G-R, but G-R-B-A, nor refer
every knowledge that tribal land is that that infected by this project.
Yeah.
Why does that act?
Under the federal policy, if there are tribal land,
which on the other hand, are considered federal land
or are in the project operation by the river,
then the United States Department of the Interior
has the opportunity to impose conditions on the license,
the impact, the impact, and the interest of the tribal lands
that are affected.
So these tribal trust lands that were in the project
of the dam were never recognized, and it attacked over 80 years,
the proceedings went forward with representation
and standing for approval for the federal land
and the project, but that's over 2016.
The tribal council is exactly the same.
Jack Delorable came and gave me a crash course on what's
happening here.
And what we've done enough of the Tribes
and the Tribes have been 2016 and for the month of May,
I want to speak to us.
of what's going on in the city, why is the level getting worse
in the last and longer after the rise?
And she came up because yet again,
GERG8 was seeking to increase the level of the lake level.
And we all know, Mr. Borske's presentation,
that when the project was established,
there was going to be a flood effect.
GERG8, who can be armed in four new
that have not gone by.
Right?
As RUKER was introduced in the lake,
the elevation was raised.
A kind of visual guy had had to have Jack breaked down
when he was simply there was less capacity
for water coming into the lake to the park.
And the design of the pool like that
is there's going to be a parking spot in the pool
for water as comes into the lake.
And each time that lake level was increased,
the parking place, the water coming into the pool
or into the lake is lost.
Where did that go?
It was upstream in the back of the pool.
So, in 2016, tracks understood
there's going to be yet another rule for change.
And the convenience management,
so first came up, it's also going to happen
that really began when the private room began
the engagement for the process.
And it was pretty stunning to us
to look at what had happened to date
and realize, boy, our interest
really were not considered at all.
We'll give you a couple of seconds.
That's what we're going to do.
When we gathered the private leaders together
and were talking about, and I said,
well, you know, the further we get to the lake
and they're no further left.
It's the product of the public.
And I've had some of the things,
for these are hand-in-saving.
That's just not true.
You know where it is.
The Senate community lost their entire Senate care.
What was what?
They had seven, all 108-year-old land,
permanently in the community.
And other private leaders had,
permanently in the day-to-day land,
being water on all the time.
And land that had water that had come on right before the flood.
So, without blood, it doesn't make sense.
We asked the Department of Interior,
what about the federal lands?
And we said, well, we're going to have to go
and we're going to have to go mad.
So, we have to go mad.
And we're going to love people all the better lands.
And for the first time in the years,
what perquisites, study decision numbers,
even the first time in the mean years,
for economic, their own federal lands.
And if I remember,
if I remember, I always had it.
Which, for example, of nothing heard,
and nothing represented in the proceedings,
had it in fact.
So, the Department of Interior, not only in the federal power,
I've not had as a role to play.
They're interested with the conditioning in the license.
Going forward that 30 to 50 year period that
Walk from Chandler, we might remember them.
They would have to say, that same would affect changes
that would benefit the quality.
We'll get to what happened to that moment.
Second example.
Cultural resources.
For eight years there had never been an evaluation
of cultural resources that were impacted from the day.
And I can tell you that when the length was filled up,
the images, some areas, cultural grounds,
we're in a minute.
Termin' remaining.
Nobody had ever done a study of what that was, what was lost.
And even after the national environmental policy
had been an evaluation of cultural resources
to be impacted from the flooding.
So, trying to keep engaged in cultural resources,
working with the staff, and never been done before.
I understand that the walkbox are here.
They're a cultural resource that's been impacted
from the day to day.
So, we're trying to keep engaged in cultural resources.
We're being moved with the staff.
They've never been done before.
I understand that the walkbox are here.
They're cultural resources.
We've been taking really effective
engaged in the processes that have really wonderful.
One of the right.
There are, there are footprints along the end of the length.
And the tributary rivers and creeks that are central
to students and plants.
Other things that are trying to keep the harvest.
And, yes, water and anything.
When water moves, it carries stuff with it.
And it had never been studied before.
It was what happens.
When heavy metals that have come down in the wind
or picked up by flood water.
And they're carried by flood water on the land.
And when that water received, what happened?
That's seven, seven, seven, seven, seven, seven, seven, seven.
So, the tributary engaged with the cities.
Folks, to take a look at what that means.
By the way, I'm exposure ahead of metals.
For people who might be harvesting plants and animals.
In the flood waters.
2012, we called the car.
We said he's identified.
About the car.
Where he said about it.
an example, diet, food, harvesting from the flood plains, and then calculated the
exporter, having medical based on those plants that we hold tested. In the next
study, an average adult over a week diet, we consume over 7,000 percent in the end of
the world. I will look at it in the 20,000, 900 percent, which you let in the only 2,300
percent of the income. Why is that? Why is that? It can get effects, the daily lives, or
problem numbers, effects, ceremonies surrounding the ground, harvesting, food, plants, and
exposing them to heavy metals and a part of this result of the operation that they had been studied
before, we're still only going to get a form of order to study. So, you've tried to
benefit, in their advocacy, and we now knew that there were federal lands involved, and that the
Department of Interior was going to have a goal. And so, if you're following that progress in the
dark night, when the men in the past, the attitude of building, that cut the tribe out of the houses,
the old people, if you've heard politicians that are good in the market, they'll tell you that
on this down of the night of the day, in this particular amendment, if we define just for this project,
not for all projects across the region, just for this project, that federal lands are not needed to
have federal lives for the purpose of this project. What that means is that the Department of Interior,
if the amendment has its intended effect, we can test that. The Department of Interior in a long
case, you can build a place in places in condition in places. If it was intended to
apply the progress that tribes have made, what we're discussing with two years, working with the
city to try to get some role for just kind of eight years in places in the process. So, we continue to engage
and we continue to work closely with the city. Like I said, the tribe shared your interest.
They share it with the government and they're committed to continuing in the relationship process.
We ensure a bunch of positive things that they can bring their interest to the table better for the product and the relationship process.
Thanks.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm a doctor.
I'm a doctor for the evening.
So, the most, even when you're out of it, see something that's inside of your son's body.
The most funny thing is about the time of night in your room.
I grew up in New Zealand, very long from the South Island, not letting us walk on a spot.
And actually, as you can hear the flowers, you're pretty somewhat to do with the issue of the room's hair and the time.
I've had a catfish and it's probably a little cold in the room.
But anyone that's very close to the start of the room.
So, my job is being women in the city.
I think that everybody's in the streets, studies have been online,
G.R.D.A. and some of us.
I'll just refer to G.R.A. today instead of name them in the South Island.
But, first of all, I'll just say once a month.
And, the model is really a simulation tool that's developed by his dog,
mathematical equations to represent physical life on the water and city.
We use those tools.
Both of the main reasons, one is we develop them to represent the same water, different flood events.
And we calibrate those to measure data, such as measured water surface of the edges.
Once we have a model calibrated, then we can adjust the width of the branches with other to some of you like.
Other than that, other than that, we can have a curve.
Now, three of these are the first ones.
The first one, we will get this in a fun route along.
We'll put some fun route in the models to protect the water surface,
our relations in brand length.
Based on both what's coming in and in files, keep out files, and based on certain rules that they must follow.
The second model is the contract model.
This is often referred to as the Copper Heads of Model of G.A.A.
In the middle of the surface, it's projected behind your reward.
Over different flights, one of the water surface elections,
one of the velocities and one of the dates,
and the leaves still is a very complicated these days.
And we're able to look almost on a minute
and walk the death velocity
and what surface salvation is,
I'll be the most forward and mindful,
even longer periods,
both all the way,
stands up its cold down,
up to Kansasville.
In the third mile of years,
the seven trance of water,
and it's good to take the changes
into a bit of our lunch.
So, I'll start a bit more of a little bit.
The first I want to talk about,
a few concepts that we've talked about tonight,
is one that's back on flight.
And this is an escape man that I've got lunch
to this lunch.
It's approximately right.
But what I chose is,
this is something,
system of G.A.A.A.A.A.
and it's saying that,
if it's called a death,
it's likely that about 75 miles upstream
of the Arkansas River coffins.
The city of Miami,
it's likely that about 135 miles upstream.
And then,
it's therefore a rich amount of 10 miles upstream from there.
Prior to the day when constructed,
the water said,
what?
What?
Charlemagne?
What's weird?
It was relatively straight,
and a very constant slope to it.
Similarly, the water surface graph
wasn't the only camera out of it.
And how much such changes,
but there's a situation that I don't want to look at now.
What happened with Damington?
There's a couple of those.
And this is my net nice little fan,
this is gray line down here.
First of all,
I'm a priest of water surface,
I'll mention,
it's a nothing,
I'm so,
I'm nearly 75 to five at its highest,
which is never crystal clear.
Further,
once you get to about 20 bridges,
we're actually a little further down in a simple area.
That water surface starts to increase
due to certain tension things.
And increases further,
it gets a little bit steeper out of the water surface,
and then,
and then, if I can,
it's off from hand,
up to all steps,
we'll encourage you to understand that.
Now,
I'm laying it to,
both of the creek hand.
And apparently in the broad cloud, and if we can clear, this is the water surface map, and this is how we'll pre-manate.
We are supposed to, water surface, come and point, come and get out.
That is the extent of all people back when we came.
And this is pretty accurate.
The journey of 2007 cloud, the water surface, how is it going to be different?
If we can tell, there's a bad one thing.
But it's a stand-to-run by 75 or more to the water.
Another point to take out is, we can see the water surface.
There's a big difference down on this problem.
And that difference kind of gets smaller, as we go through the landscape.
So one of the key questions that have been talked about on these studies is,
what kind of is it we love the water surface elevation down?
Well, you're still at a different speed.
That won't be a problem.
I'll be able to imagine that.
We could have done it for the water surface.
And that's what many of these studies are looking at.
It's one of the impacts of changing the water surface elevation down in the water.
Now, this is, sort of, another schematic that I've heard of, this is a cross-section,
because that was right to the city of Miami.
And it's actually at the Miami Gadget.
Now, the sky was a little misleading because the cross-section law
was going to go to 2000 to 2000 to 2000 to 2000.
So the purpose of the show is that the easement is that the elevation is still in the 60.
That's what's in the salvation.
It's where it would be, about the 2000s of the flood, if it didn't be my damn boss.
So the easement would have been easily exceeded even if not bad in the place in Miami.
Now, it would be down in place.
The water surface elevation actually increased up to about seven to five.
Now, for grandparents, I've sort of got my own right on the left hand side here,
and it's a bit confusing.
I've got my own right hand side.
I'm a section here, which is the bottom of the channel.
Now, we might as well scale as a little bit of the studio here.
One of the shows is, even a small increase in faith
ends up resulting in a wide increase in the land of the state of the flood.
It's just kind of a scene where there's already a move to this.
This is the real good from here.
It might seem to have been connected by today and the real good.